Frances Hooper Papers on Virginia Woolf, 1915-1986
Mortimer Rare Book Room, William Allan Neilson Library, Smith College
- Series IV. Writings Of Others, 1927-1985
  - Woolf, Virginia. "Aurora Leigh," "Letter To a Young Poet," and "A Conversation About Art" From The Yale Review. 1931 Jun (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Woolf, Virginia. "A Conversation About Art."
    See: Box 3, folder 68.
  - Woolf, Virginia. "Ellen Terry": photostat. From The New Statesman and Nation. 1941 Feb 8 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Woolf, Virginia. "Gissing's 'By the Ionian Sea'." (Box 3, Folder 69a)
  - Woolf, Virginia. "Letter To a Young Poet."
    See: Box 3, folder 68
  - Woolf, Virginia. "Mrs. Thrale": photostat. From The New Statesman and Nation. 1941 Mar 8 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Woolf, Virginia. "The New Dress." From Forum. 1927 May (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Woolf, Virginia. "On Not Knowing Greek": photocopy. From The Common Reader. n.d. (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Series V. Reviews, 1930-1985
  - Annan, Noel
    See: Box 4, folder 108
  - Bates, Ralph
    See: Box 3, folder 73
  - Bell, Quentin. Virginia Woolf.
  - Bennett, Arnold
    See: Box 3, folder 84a
  - Bennett, Joan. Virginia Woolf: Her Art As a Novelist. 1945 Feb-Sep (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Blackwood, Caroline
    See: Box 3, folder 84
  - Bowen, Elizabeth
    See: Box 4, folder 109
  - Brown, John Mason
    See: Box 3, folder 103
  - Butscher, Fanny
    See: Box 3, folder 75
  - Constable, Rosalind
    See: Box 3, folder 101
  - Cruttwell, Patrick
    See: Box 3, folder 80
  - Edel, Leon. Bloomsbury: A House of Lions. 1979 Jun 19 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Four Americans in Paris.
  - Freedman, Richard
    See: Box 3, folder 78
  - Gathorne-Hardy, Robert. Ottoline at Garsington.
    See: Box 3, folder 98
  - Gordon, Caroline. The Woman on the Porch. 1944 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Gordon, Lyndall. Virginia Woolf: A Writer's Life. 1985 Mar 17 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Gray, James
  - Gregory, Horace
    See: Box 3, folder 85
  - Kronenberger, Louis
    See: Box 3, folder 77
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S. Collector's Progress.
  - Mansfield, Katherine. Novels and Novelists. 1930 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Maxwell, William
  - Murray, Michele
  - Prescott, Peter S.
    See: Box 3, folder 74
  - Rilla, W. P.
  - Ruskamp, Judith Sara
    See: Box 3, folder 76
  - Sayre, Nora
  - Smith, Harrison
  - Stein, Gertrude. Gertrude Stein on Picasso.
  - Tennant, Emma
  - The Virginia Woolf Reader
  - Wagenknecht, Edward
    See: Box 3, folder 79
  - Welty, Eudora
    See: Box 3, folder 82
  - Woolf, Leonard. The Journey Not the Arrival Matters. 1970 Mar 29 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Woolf, Leonard. Downhill All the Way.
  - Woolf, Virginia. The Captain's Death Bed. 1950 May (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Woolf, Virginia. Collected Essays. 1967 Nov 19 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Woolf, Virginia. The Diary of Virginia Woolf.
  - Woolf, Virginia. Flush. 1933 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Woolf, Virginia. A Haunted House, And Other Short Stories. 1944 Apr 16 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Woolf, Virginia. The Letters of Virginia Woolf. n.d. (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Woolf, Virginia. Moments of Being. 1976 Jul 22 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Woolf, Virginia. Orlando. 1928 Nov 8 (Box 3, Folder 84a)
  - Woolf, Virginia. The Second Common Reader. 1932 Oct 30 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Woolf, Virginia. A Writer's Diary.
- Series VI. Subject Files, 1925-1980
  - Albee, Edward. Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?: playbill and article. 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Art n.d. (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Austria n.d. (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bedford, Mary du Caurroy Russell, Duchess of, 1865-1937 1968 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Beecham, Thomas, Sir, 1878-1961 1974 Oct 3 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Bowen, Elizabeth, 1899-1973 1968 Nov 10 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Cameron, Julia Margaret Prattle, 1815-1879 1946 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Fuller, Margaret, 1810-1850: engraved portrait by H. B. Hall, Jr. n.d. (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Hawthorne, Nathaniel, 1804-1864 n.d. (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Hogarth Press 1947 Nov (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Horan, Kenneth O'Donnell, Mrs., born 1890 1942 Dec 20 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Johnson, Samuel, 1709-1784 n.d. (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Morrell, Ottoline Violet Anne Cavendish-Bentinck, Lady, 1873-1938 1974 Sep 26 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Music 1980 Nov 17 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Smith College 1914-1925 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Stein, Gertrude, 1874-1946 1971 Jan 31 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Trollope, Frances Milton, 1780-1863 n.d. (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Walpole, Horace, 1717-1797 1951 Sep 22 (Box 3, Folder 103)
- Series VII. Photographs, 1927-1985
  - Hooper, Frances 1954 Apr 19 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    See also: Box 4, folder 110
  - Woolf, Virginia 1927 (Box 3, Folder 105)
- Series Oversize, 1947-1985
  - Correspondence
    - Gomme, Laurence 1947-1951 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Northwestern University Library 1982 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Reviews
    - Bell, Quentin. Virginia Woolf. 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Woolf, Virginia. A Writer's Diary. 1954 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Photographs
    - Hooper, Frances 1985 Jun (Box 4, Folder 110)